Guide to the Batya Weinbaum papers, 1960-2015 RL.11482
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Teaching, 1983-2011; 8
  - Course Materials, 8.1
    - Teaching Feminism Online (Box 34)
    - Teaching philosophy (Box 35)
    - English 115- The American Experience (Box 35)
    - Asian-American Literature materials (Box 35)
    - Bamboo Girl, Issue 10 (Box 35)
    - CSU electives- Middle Eastern Studies, 1998-2000 (Box 35)
    - CSU electives- African American Studies, 1998-2000 (Box 35)
    - Philosophy for teaching Women's Studies (Box 35)
    - Notes Goffman-Asylums (Box 35)
    - Women's Liberation Movement (Box 35)
    - English 208- African American Literature and Womanism (Box 35)
    - Asian-American poetry cards (Box 35)
    - Evaluation of Feminist Approches to the Classics, 2002 (Box 35)
    - FAAR Earl's sample course (Box 35)
    - Restockings, 2008 (Box 35)
    - Women's Studies 102 (Box 35)
    - Multicultural studies student breakdown, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Multicultural children's books (Box 35)
    - Interview- Carla Gerran and Keller Schwartz (Box 35)
    - Syllabus- Women's Oral History (Box 35)
    - Integrated Language Arts Program Development Guide (Box 35)
    - CSU electives- Multicultural Studies, 2000 (Box 35)
    - The Feminism of Time Magazine, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Syllabus- Womanism and Feminism, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Anne Cudnik graduate assistant work (Box 36)
    - English 348 student work (Box 36)
    - Evelyn Stewart coursework, 2003 (Box 36)
    - Diversity in Women's Liberation Ideology readings (Box 36)
    - Humanising Housing (Box 36)
    - Protective Rules for Consciousness Raising (Box 36)
    - The Sixties Speak to the Eighties, 1983-10-22 (Box 36)
    - Restockings manifesto (Box 36)
    - Womanism and Feminism, 1999 (Box 36)
    - English 347 consciousness raising project, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Project hand-out women and feminism (Box 36)
    - English 208 (Box 36)
    - Womanism and Feminism, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Womanism and Feminism attendance, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Womanism and Feminism readings and book list, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Womanism and Feminism blank evaluation forms, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Angels and Amazons (Box 36)
    - The Declaration of Sentiments of the Seneca Falls Convention (Box 36)
    - Angela Davis speaks at Oberlin, 1998-04 (Box 36)
    - Black Women in the United States an Abbreviated Chronology (Box 36)
    - Student assignments, 2001 (Box 37)
    - English 348/548 Coralia Ciurcel paper, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Beats- Jerrod Jacobs paper (Box 37)
    - Beats- Web page poetry (Box 37)
    - English 363- Sandy Farraj (Box 37)
    - English 330, 2000 (Box 37)
    - English 695 Beyond Realism packet (Box 37)
    - Beats- Dan Husek paper (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- The Civil Rights Movement (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- The Great Mother (Box 37)
    - CSU course syllabi, 1996 (Box 37)
    - Teaching support ideas (Box 37)
    - Thesis Maxfield- working outline (Box 37)
    - Women and the New Left (Box 37)
    - Women of the World Unite (Box 37)
    - Whoopi Goldberg (Box 37)
    - Crusader Crusader for Justice (Box 37)
    - Whatever Happened to Women? (Box 37)
    - What Can Be Learned: A Critique of the Miss America Protest (Box 37)
    - To Tell the Truth Freely (Box 37)
    - Who is Your Mother: Red Roots of White Feminism (Box 37)
    - To the Seeker of Truth (Box 37)
    - Jews and Hollywood (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- Jews and Hollywood (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- Hispanics in the United States (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- Qualitative Research, 1999 (Box 37)
    - Syllabus- Anthropology, 1998 (Box 37)
    - Asian-American Literature syllabi (Box 37)
    - Course materials electronic records, 2003-2011; 228 document and image files; approximately 24 MB. (Digital-materials RL11482-SET-0001)
  - Administrative, 8.2
    - English 208/347 student evaluations, 1998 (Box 38)
    - CSU application materials (Box 38)
    - CSU faculty application (Box 38)
    - Research and scholarship list, 1998-1999 (Box 38)
    - Promotion workshop for assistant professors, 2001-03-21 (Box 38)
    - Personal statement (Box 38)
    - Batya resume, 2013 (Box 38)
    - OU Handbook on Ethics, 2002 (Box 38)
    - CSU Faculty Activities Report, 2001-2002 (Box 38)
    - CSU Faculty Activities Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 38)
    - CSU graduate faculty membership, 1998 (Box 38)
    - Course evaluations, 1999-2001 (Box 38)
    - CSU Teaching Observation Report, 2002-06-05 (Box 38)
    - CSU class rosters, 1998-2000 (Box 38)
    - Solicitation of papers in general education classes, 2000 (Box 38)
    - CSU Grant Research Request, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Committee on Instruction memorandums and agendas, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Office Space Action Request, 2001 (Box 38)
    - Batya behavior request (Box 38)
    - CSU chilly working environment (Box 38)
    - Department handbooks, 2000-2002 (Box 38)
    - Diversity in Education- Classroom Resource Manual, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Agreement CSU and American Association of University Professors (Box 39)
    - CSU Poetry Center (Box 39)
    - CSU operating budget, 2000-2001 (Box 39)
    - NEH summer stipend, 1998-09 (Box 39)
    - Release time proposal, 1999-02 (Box 39)
    - University Catalogues, 2000-2002 (Box 39)
    - Student evaluations, 1999 (Box 39)
    - Proof of posting- Assistant Professor of Poetry, 2001 (Box 39)
    - Carol disability letter (Box 39)
    - Proposed revisions- Standards and Evaluation Guidelines of the Oral History Association, 1998 (Box 39)
    - Graduate assistant- Tuition Grant Agreement, 1998 (Box 39)
    - CSU Libraries Year-end Report, 1999-07 (Box 39)
    - Teacher evalautions, 2001 (Box 39)
    - Multicultural Studies minor, 2000 (Box 39)
    - Multicultural literature articles (Box 39)
    - Multiculturalism Task Force, 1999 (Box 39)
    - Proposal for Multicultural Literature Concentration, 2001 (Box 39)
    - Multiculturalism Task Force survey responses (Box 39)
    - Meeting notes- Teaching multiculturalism (Box 39)
    - Resource Manual- Diversity in Education, 1996 (Box 39)
    - Pacifica course evaluations, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Course evaluation summaries, 1998-2001 (Box 40)
    - The Strategist- Tips and Tactics for Women Faculty, 1998 (Box 40)
    - CSU Women's Studies faculty list (Box 40)
    - CSU Fourth Year Review, 2001 (Box 40)
    - Women's Comprehensive Program request, 1998 (Box 40)
    - Women's Studies course write-up samples, 1999 (Box 40)
    - CSU class rosters, 2002 (Box 40)
    - Henry Woodburn Fellowship application, 1984 (Box 40)
    - CSU affirmative action form, 1998 (Box 40)
    - CSU course evaluations (Box 40)
    - Empire State College Study evaluation, 2011 (Box 40)
    - CSU budget codes (Box 40)
    - CSU book purchasing procedure, 1999 (Box 40)
    - Department of English committees and assignments (Box 40)
    - CSU class rosters, 2001 (Box 40)
    - CSU by-laws Department of English (Box 40)
    - Kyle Bostian- Candidate comment sheet, 2003 (Box 40)
    - Course evaluations, 1998-1999 (Box 40)
    - Course proposals (Box 40)
    - Chair evaluation, 2000 (Box 40)
    - COI License, 2001-10 (Box 40)
    - Classroom visits, 2001 (Box 40)
- Photography, 1970-2012; 9
  - Chile- Day Care, Valdiva (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Independence Day Parade, Bocha Bamoa (Box 42)
  - Chile- San Grigorio (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Antiplano Dances, La Paz (Box 42)
  - Chile- Nueva Havana (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Cumbre (Box 42)
  - Chile- Lucho's farm, Cauntin and Gladys at home, Valdiva (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Zipaquira families (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Bogota school (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Cali Cafes (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Minuto de Dios (Box 42)
  - Chille- Hospital, Rio Buemo and Daycare, Valdiva (Box 42)
  - Chile- Baptism, slum housing (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Cali family (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Bogota (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Cali street scenes (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Family Orphanage, San Francisco (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Mother's Club-Arque, Cochabamba (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- parades (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- School children, parade, mothers clubs (Box 42)
  - Peru- Machu Picchu (Box 42)
  - Peru- Tourists (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Combre (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Children in school uniforms (Box 42)
  - Ecuador- Hospital home weavers (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Doctor in Bodeo, Cochabamba (Box 42)
  - Bolivia- Hospitals, home (Box 42)
  - Colombia- Orphanage, San Francisco (Box 42)
  - Cuba- Churches (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Matanzas Seminary (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Miscellaneous (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Daycare, La Habana (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Tobacco factory (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Primary school (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Street scenes, housing and balconies (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Nurse treating child, Escuela el campo (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Voodoo Museum (Box 43)
  - Cuba- Hebrew school, Havana (Box 43)
  - China- Shanghai, 1978 (Box 43)
  - West coast trip, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Chile- Lucho's asemthmiento, J.J. Collhor Cautin (Box 43)
  - Chile- Daycare, Milk program, contraceptive clinic (Box 43)
  - Cera Fidel Castra Aprofa Meeting (Box 43)
  - Ecuador- Quito, St. Kids (Box 43)
  - Ecuador- Quito restaurants (Box 43)
  - Chile- School, Gladysse Marcella (Box 43)
  - Chile- Daycare, Puento Alto (Box 43)
  - Chile- Daycare, Gilde Castro (Box 43)
  - Ecuador- Saquisquille schools (Box 43)
  - Ecuador- Cuenca family (Box 43)
  - Ecuador- Hospital, Cuenca (Box 43)
  - Chile- Agricultural skill schools (Box 43)
  - Chile- Rural school, Mehuim (Box 43)
  - Chile- Technical schools, daycare (Box 43)
  - Bolivia- Hospital, personnel school (Box 43)
  - Chile- Mother's center teenagers (Box 43)
  - Colombia- Old women, Zipaquira (Box 43)
  - Chile- Bolina, Gladia at home (Box 43)
  - Chile- Contraceptive clinic, San Grigorio, Santiago (Box 43)
  - Chile- Daycare hospital, Barro-Lucos Trudum (Box 43)
  - Assorted matted photos (Box 44)
  - Central Park (Box 44)
  - New York City (Box 44)
  - Chile- Assorted negatives, 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Norma Rita Video (Box 44)
  - Paul and Irene, 2012 (Box 44)
  - New York, 1970 (Box 44)
  - Woodstock (Box 44)
  - Women and archetypes (Box 44)
  - Photos for dissertation, 1990-1995 (Box 44)
  - Woman saxaphonist, Jerusalem, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Ola and her father (Box 44)
  - Published UNICEF photo (Box 44)
  - Bali beach (Box 44)
  - Photocopies- Island women pictures (Box 44)
  - Female community leaders, 1998-1999 (Box 44)
  - Batya and Ola negatives (Box 44)
  - Assorted photos, 1990-2001 (Box 45)
  - Ola school photos (Box 45)
  - Red Serpent Clothing modeling (Box 45)
  - Assorted negatives, 1990-2001 (Box 45)
  - Old birthday, 1999-12 (Box 45)
  - Code Pink protest photos (Box 45)
  - Israeli women negatives and contact sheets, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Batya and artist, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Family album, undated, 1968 (Box 45)
  - Isla photos with captions, 1992 (Box 46)
  - Baby Ola in Cozumel, Mexico (Box 46)
  - Batya portraits (Box 46)
  - Community of the Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 46)
  - Baby Ola and early childhood photos (Box 46)
  - Batya and Ola prints, 2009 (Box 46)
  - Batya friends, 1980-1989 (Box 46)
  - Assorted negatives, 2002-2003 (Box 46)
  - Mexico negatives, 2006 (Box 46)
  - Polaroid print-outs (Box 46)
  - Assorted photos, 2002-2003 (Box 46)
  - Babies, 2002-2003 (Box 46)
  - Display in Field Museum Chicago- Mexico photograph (Box 46)
  - Print-outs of Mexico negatives and contact sheets (Box 46)
  - Red Serpent Clothing photo album, 2006 (Box 46)
  - Batya's family members (Box 46)
  - Batya's high school boyfriend (Box 46)
  - Artist portrait (Box 46)
  - Assorted portraits contact sheets (Box 46)
  - Photo album, 1990-1999 (Box 46)
  - Photo album, 1990-2000 (Box 47)
  - Protest, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Evanston and Coney Island (Box 47)
    - Teptzlan Mexico with Michael, 1970-1979 (Box 47)
  - Amy at school (Box 47)
  - Exhibition content (Box 47)
  - Show, 1974-02 (Box 47)
  - Graphics from The Island of Women, 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Isla Mujeres, 1992 (Box 47)
  - Mexico prints (Box 47)
  - FEMSPEC slides (Box 47)
  - Bolivia health (Box 47)
  - Photo album, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Photo album, 1999 (Box 48)
  - Hula (Box 48)
  - Photos for Israeli Peace Movement book (Box 48)
  - Assorted slides (Box 48)
  - Jack Weinbaum photos and death certificate (Box 48)
  - Grandparents (Box 48)
  - Ola and her dog (Box 48)
  - Photo album- Ola baby (Box 48)
  - Photo album, 1990-1995 (Box 48)
  - Photo album, 1988-1990 (Box 48)
  - Photo album, 1991-1995 (Box 48)
  - Cuba-UNICEF truck (Box 49)
  - Chile- Prints (Box 49)
  - Chile- Assorted negatives and contact sheets (Box 49)
  - Batya with camera (Box 49)
  - Summer, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Hampshire, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Toronto home photos (Box 49)
  - Central Square (Box 49)
  - Assorted contact sheets and negatives, 1970-1979; 15 folders (Box 49)
  - Ladies doing laundry- print (Box 50)
  - Freelance work- Boston, 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Assorted contact sheets and negatives, 1970-1979; 13 folders (Box 50)
  - Exhibition photographs (Box 80)
  - Digital photographs, 2004-2011; 349 digital image files; approximatley 187 MB. (Digital-materials RL11482-SET-0001)
- Print Materials, 1971-2013; 10
  - Periodicals, 10.1
    - Thought Crime, v. 3, no. 2-3, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Lesbian Connection, v. 34, no. 2,4, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - West End, v. 4, no. 3, 1977 (Box 51)
    - Sinister Wisdom, no. 87, 2012 (Box 51)
    - Women of Power, no. 3, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Old Crow, no. 3, 1992 (Box 51)
    - The Mind's Eye, 2003 (Box 51)
    - UMass- Spectrum, 1981 (Box 51)
    - La Mujer, v. 2, no. 1-3, 1971 (Box 51)
    - isie, v. 5, no. 3, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Flower, no. 6, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Feminary, v. 10, no. 1, 1981 (Box 51)
    - The Feminist Art Journal, v. 6, no. 1, 1977 (Box 51)
    - Communities at Large Letter, no. 10, 1997 (Box 51)
    - UNICEF news, no. 75, 1973 (Box 51)
    - Iowa Women, v. 13, no. 3, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Israel Horizons, v. 41, no. 2, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Gypsy, no. 21-22, 1993-1994 (Box 51)
    - The Oral History Review, v. 15 no. 2, 1987 (Box 52)
    - SFRA Review, no. 244, 246, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Long Long Ago, v. 3, no. 4 (Box 52)
    - Old Crow, no. 4, 1993 (Box 52)
    - Sage Woman, no. 83, 2011 (Box 52)
    - Key West Review, v. 2, no. 1-2, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Taboo, v. 8, no. 1, 2004 (Box 52)
    - The Journal of Progressive Judaism, no. 12, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Quest: A Feminist Quarterly, v. 5, no. 2, 1980 (Box 52)
    - Heresies, no. 15, 1982 (Box 52)
    - Feminist Collections, v. 34, no. 1-2, 2013 (Box 52)
    - Off Our Backs, v. 33, no. 1-2, 2003 (Box 52)
    - UNICEF news, no. 74, 1972-1973 (Box 52)
    - Maize: A Lesbian Country Magazine, no. 84, 2008 (Box 52)
    - Magic Realism, v. 5, no. 2, 1996 (Box 52)
    - Comic book- Dynamite Damsels (Box 52)
    - Other Tongue, v. 2, no. 1, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Kindred Sisters, 2013-08 (Box 53)
    - Independent Arts Quarterly Home Planet News, no. 32, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Big Fish, no. 12, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Rain and Thunder, no. 37, 51, 2007-2011 (Box 53)
    - Iowa Women, v. 14, no. 3-4, 1994-1995 (Box 53)
    - Iowa Women, v. 13, no. 2, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Spectrum: Words and Images, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Phoenix Rising, v. 2, no. 3, 1981 (Box 53)
    - The Review of Radical Political Economics, v. 9, no. 3, 1977 (Box 53)
    - The Review of Radical Political Economics, v. 8, no. 2, 1976 (Box 53)
    - The Review of Radical Political Economics, v. 8, no. 1, 1976 (Box 53)
    - Heresies, no. 12, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Tikkun, v. 19, no. 1, 2004 (Box 53)
    - The Vindicator, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Magic Realism, v. 4, no. 2, 1993 (Box 53)
    - Off Our Backs, v. 36, no. 1, 2006 (Box 53)
    - Studies in American Jewish Literature, v. 24, 2005 (Box 54)
    - Studies in American Jewish Literature, v. 20, 2001 (Box 54)
    - Bridges, v. 13, no. 1, 2008 (Box 54)
    - conditions, v. 1, no. 2, 1977 (Box 54)
    - Foundation, v. 36, no. 101, 2007 (Box 54)
    - Extrapolation, v. 44, no. 1; v. 45, no. 3; v. 44, no. 1, 2003-2008 (Box 54)
    - Tales of the Unanticipated, no. 25, 2004-2005 (Box 54)
    - Journal of Scholarly Publishing, v. 34, no. 4, 2003 (Box 54)
    - Monthly Review, v. 28, no. 3, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Heresies, no. 6, 1978 (Box 55)
    - Boskone, no. 28, 1991-02 (Box 55)
    - Sinister Wisdom, no. 36, 71, 1988-2007 (Box 55)
    - Sinister Wisdom, no. 73, 2008 (Box 55)
    - Catharsis, v. 3, no. 2, 1993 (Box 55)
    - MELUS, v. 23, no. 3, 1998 (Box 55)
    - Journal of Feminist Family Therapy, v. 13, no. 4, 2001 (Box 55)
    - Anything That Moves, no. 2, 4, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
    - NWSA Journal, v. 21, no. 2, 2009 (Box 56)
    - NWSA Journal, v. 10, no. 3, 1998 (Box 56)
    - Mothering, Sex and Sexuality, v. 4, no. 1, 2002 (Box 56)
  - Books, 10.2
    - 40th Anniversary Alumni Art Exhibition Catalogue (Box 56)
    - Twilight, 1995 (Box 56)
    - Art: Tempo of Today, 1969 (Box 56)
    - Advance readers copy- Helluva Luxe, 2012 (Box 56)
    - Where have all the flower children gone?, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Down the Birth Canal: record of a pregnancy, 2014 (Box 56)
    - Opening Palms: Volume 2, 2013 (Box 56)
    - Opening Palms: Volume 1, 2010 (Box 56)
    - A Dyke's Bike Repair Handbook, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Milk and Honey: A Celebration of Jewish Lesbian Poetry, 2011 (Box 56)
    - Nice Jewish, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Second-place Rebels: Beat Women in a Man's Generation, 2002 (Box 56)
    - Fragments of Motherhood, 1996 (Box 56)
    - Annotated copy- Beat Hotel, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Ways of Knowing in and Through the Body: Diverse Perspectives on Embodiment (Box 56)
    - Pictures of Patriarchy, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Annotated copy- Operation Shylock, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Annotated copy- Triton, 1976 (Box 56)
    - Word of Mouth, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Re-placing America: Conversations and Contestations, 2000 (Box 56)
    - Into Darkness Peering: Race and Color in the Fantastic, 1997 (Box 56)
    - "Lost on the Map of the World", 2001 (Box 56)
- Family Memorabilia, 1989-2011; 12
  - Scrapbooks, 12.1
    - Newspaper box (Box 77)
    - Scrapbook, 1993 (Box 77)
    - Scrapbook- poetry in India, 2005 (Box 77)
    - Scrapbook, 2000 (Box 77)
    - Scrapbook, 1992-2007 (Box 77)
    - Scrapbook- UNICEF photos (Box 79)
    - Scrapbook- advertisements (Box 79)
  - Ola Weinbaum, 12.2
    - Ola schoolwork- high school (Box 78)
    - National Youth Leadership Forum, 2008 (Box 78)
    - Ola service hours (Box 78)
    - Mom's Apple Pie- birth announcement (Box 78)
    - Caricature drawing (Box 78)
    - Sonogram (Box 78)
    - Cards for Batya (Box 78)
    - Ola schoolwork- elementary school, 1998-2003 (Box 78)
    - Ola home report- grade 5.7 (Box 78)
    - Writing practice (Box 78)
    - Drawings for Batya (Box 78)
    - Performing arts, 2000-2006 (Box 78)
    - Baby headband (Box 78)
    - Winter scene drawing, 2003-12 (Box 83)
    - Thanksgiving poem (Box 83)
    - Things that Matter book (Box 83)
    - Draft- 18th Birthday book (Box 83)
    - 18th Birthday book, 2010; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Name badges (Box 83)
    - Guilford College acceptance letter, 2010 (Box 83)
    - National Society of High School Scholars award, 2010 (Box 83)
    - Red Rose Dog Cafe (Box 83)
    - Ola poetry (Box 83)
    - School awards (Box 83)
    - Ola Weinbaum electronic records, 2003-2011; 356 document and image files; approximately 59 MB. (Digital-materials RL11482-SET-0001)
  - Other, 12.3
    - Assorted bookmarks (Box 83)
    - Assorted business cards (Box 83)
    - Weinbaum estate auction (Box 83)
    - Mayan playing deck and palmistry (Box 83)
    - Wall of Tolerance certificate, 2005-09 (Box 83)
    - Black Eel's papers (Box 83)
    - Israeli passport (Box 83)
    - Shooting range target (Box 83)
    - Astrology (Box 83)
    - Other electronic records, 2004-2011; 38 document files; approximately 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL11482-SET-0001)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1992-2007; 13
  - Floppy Disks, 13.1
    - Space and Frontier in Leslie F. Stone (Box 81)
    - Stone Stories- The Rape of the Solar System; The Hell Planet (Box 81)
    - Out of the Void I; Out of the Void II; Across the Void I, 2 disks (Box 81)
    - Across the Void II; Across the Void III, 2 disks (Box 81)
    - The Conquest of Gola and Other Stories, 1996 (Box 81)
    - Stone Stories- The Fall of Mercury (Box 81)
    - Out of the Void- excerpt (Box 81)
    - Brooke (Box 81)
    - Brooke- book and articles (Box 81)
    - Sasha's Harlem (Box 81)
    - Israel interviews, 2000-2001 (Box 81)
    - Radio prologue (Box 81)
    - Ola's work (Box 81)
    - Surveys and contact list, 2000 (Box 81)
    - Girl Power Issue- FEMSPEC, 2 disks (Box 81)
    - Real Time (Box 81)
    - Debra Shaw- Sex and the Single Starship Captain (Box 81)
    - Stone book- final version, 2000-09-11 (Box 81)
    - Megan Musgrave- Phenomenal Women (Box 81)
    - Passionate Spark, 2001 (Box 81)
    - Hula (Box 81)
    - Comic strip from CSU struggle (Box 81)
    - Native American Issue- FEMSPEC, 2000-02-02 (Box 81)
    - Kate Austin- Orion (Box 81)
    - Feminist speculative art text and images (Box 81)
    - Meridith Peterson (Box 81)
    - Rosenberg- Suburban Fantasy (Box 81)
    - Debra Shleaf- From the Archives, 2005-09; 2 disks (Box 81)
    - Void story (Box 81)
    - CE Lexington Bks. Test (Box 81)
    - MC Transcript- Karla and Kaila (Box 81)
    - Stone lecture (Box 81)
    - Carlen Lavigne- Melodrama, Feminism and the Women of Farscape, 2004-01-21 (Box 81)
    - Editor's self interview (Box 81)
    - Batya photo (Box 81)
    - menwwing (Box 81)
    - Computer backup, 1999; 4 disks (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC calls and letters, 1999-12-31 (Box 81)
    - Jerusalem poetry (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC, v. 2, no. 2, 2 disks (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC, v. 1, no. 1 (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC, v. 3, no. 1, 2 disks (Box 81)
    - Kaila Schwartz- Trickster in Children's Books of Louise Eldrich (Box 81)
    - Fambrough- Birthing (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC files from Lee (Box 81)
    - Elijah's Eyes (Box 81)
    - Aliyah Strauss; Hannah Safron (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC cover (Box 81)
    - Computer backup, 1992 (Box 81)
    - FEMSPEC status report, 2002-05-15 (Box 81)
    - Computer backup, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
    - Xena books (Box 81)
    - Kafka on Sexuality (Box 81)
    - Poetry, 1994 (Box 82)
    - Novels, 1994; 4 disks (Box 83)
  - Cassettes, 13.2
    - Mini-cassettes, 4 tapes (Box 81)
    - Interview- Hollis of Hulaui Hilo (Box 82)
    - Flying Hands Plays- Batya piano recording, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Flying Hands Plays- Life Song Movement for the Ancestors (Box 82)
    - Amy Vagi- English 347 (Box 82)
    - The Legacy of Franz Boas for a Multicultural Analysis of Jews and Issues in Race (Box 82)
    - Performing "Americanness": The Theatricalization of Jewish Identity (Box 82)
    - Women in Black, 1990 (Box 82)
    - Shoshannah Harrari (Box 82)
    - Umass recordings, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Mauve mixtape (Box 82)
  - VHS tapes, 13.3
    - Class, 1998-11-17 (Box 82)
    - Business 208, 2002-11-19 (Box 82)
    - Jean Day- Natural Movement Into Dance, 1998-05-22 (Box 82)
  - DVD-ROMs, 13.4
    - Using Palmistry to Change Your Life (Box 82)
  - CD-ROMs, 13.5
    - FEMSPEC, v. 3, no. 2 (Box 82)
    - FEMSPEC, v. 4, no. 1 (Box 82)
    - FEMSPEC, v. 1, no. 2- supplement, 2 disks (Box 82)
    - Zeitgeist Addendum (Box 82)
    - Hawaiin Rhapsody Piano (Box 82)
    - Batya Weinbaum, 2007-05-22; 3 disks (Box 82)
    - Hard drive contents, 2004 (Box 82)